"If you could
wake up tomorrow
"having gained any
one quality or ability,
what would it be?"
(Penny:)Well, not to steal
from the Bible,
(Penny:)but turning water into wine
sounds pretty good.
(Sheldon:)I don't think you're
taking this seriously.
(Penny:)Come on, I'm just having
some fun with you.
(Sheldon:)I believe
what you're doing is using humor
(Sheldon:)to avoid vulnerability.
(Howard:)Fine.
(Penny:)Honestly...
(Penny:)if I could have one quality...
(Penny:)I wish I could be
as smart as you guys.
Ha! Keep dreaming.
Sheldon!
(Clerk:)I'm sorry.
(Shedon:)That was me having
fun with you.
(Sheldon:)Look.
(Shedon:)You may not be as...
(Shedon:)academically inclined as are we.
(Shedon:)Yes, that's how you say it.
(Sheldon:)But...
(Shedon:)You possess an
intelligence I envy.